{
"question": "何故",
"answer": "なぜ"
},
{
"question": "一日",
"answer": "いちにち"
},
{
"question": "寒い",
"answer": "さむい"
},
{
"question": "見せる",
"answer": "みせる"
},
{
"question": "違う",
"answer": "ちがう"
},
{
"question": "如何して",
"answer": "どうして"
},
{
"question": "付ける",
"answer": "つける"
},
{
"question": "覚える",
"answer": "おぼえる"
},
{
"question": "近く",
"answer": "ちかく"
},
{
"question": "風",
"answer": "かぜ"
},
{
"question": "困る",
"answer": "こまる"
},
{
"question": "生まれる",
"answer": "うまれる"
},
{
"question": "丁度",
"answer": "ちょうど"
},
{
"question": "初めて",
"answer": "はじめて"
},
{
"question": "始まる",
"answer": "はじまる"
},
{
"question": "貸す",
"answer": "かす"
},
{
"question": "奇麗",
"answer": "きれい"
},
{
"question": "幾ら",
"answer": "いくら"
},
{
"question": "空-1",
"answer": "そら"
},
{
"question": "弾く-1",
"answer": "ひく"
},
